{"shortAnswer": [{"Question": "Describe 'Computer networks'.", "Answer": "If the truth be told, computer networks are a pain to set up.", "originalSentence": "If the truth be told, computer networks are a pain to set up."}, {"Question": "Describe 'File server'.", "Answer": "A computer whose main purpose in life is to host shared hard drives is called a file server.", "originalSentence": "A computer whose main purpose in life is to host shared hard drives is called a file server."}, {"Question": "Describe 'Network'.", "Answer": "\u2726 The cheaper and less powerful computers in a network are the clients.", "originalSentence": "\u2726 The cheaper and less powerful computers in a network are the clients."}, {"Question": "Describe 'Clients\u2019'.", "Answer": "Clients are the computers used by individual users for everyday work.", "originalSentence": "Clients are the computers used by individual users for everyday work."}, {"Question": "Describe 'Server computer'.", "Answer": "Dedicated Servers and Peers In some networks, a server computer is a server computer and nothing else.", "originalSentence": "Dedicated Servers and Peers In some networks, a server computer is a server computer and nothing else."}, {"Question": "Explain the following with an example: 'In some cases, other types of connections are used.'", "Answer": "In most cases, this connection is made via electrical cables that carry the information in the form of electrical signals. But in some cases, other types of connections are used.For example, fiber-optic cables let computers communicate at extremely high speeds by using impulses of light.", "originalSentence": "But in some cases, other types of connections are used."}, {"Question": "Explain the following with an example: 'Windows'", "Answer": "They usually run a desktop version of Windows such as Windows XP Professional, along with application software such as Microsoft Office.", "originalSentence": "They usually run a desktop version of Windows such as Windows XP Professional, along with application software such as Microsoft Office."}, {"Question": "Explain the following with an example: 'Client computers are sometimes referred to as workstations. Server computers typically run a specialized net- work operating system such as Windows Server 2003, NetWare, or Linux, along with special software to provide network services.'", "Answer": "Client computers are sometimes referred to as workstations. Server computers typically run a specialized net- work operating system such as Windows Server 2003, NetWare, or Linux, along with special software to provide network services.For example, a server may run Microsoft Exchange to provide e-mail services for the network, or it may run Apache Web Server so that the computer can serve Web pages.", "originalSentence": "Server computers typically run a specialized net- work operating system such as Windows Server 2003, NetWare, or Linux, along with special software to provide network services."}, {"Question": "Explain the following with an example: 'The most common way of sharing information is to share individual files.'", "Answer": "The most common way of sharing information is to share individual files.For example, two or more people can work together on a single spreadsheet file or word-processing document.", "originalSentence": "The most common way of sharing information is to share individual files."}, {"Question": "Explain the following with an example: 'In most networks, a large hard drive on a central server computer is set up as a common storage area where users can store files to be shared with other users.'", "Answer": "In most networks, a large hard drive on a central server computer is set up as a common storage area where users can store files to be shared with other users.For example, messaging applications let network users exchange messages with each other using an e-mail appli- cation such as Microsoft Outlook.", "originalSentence": "In most networks, a large hard drive on a central server computer is set up as a common storage area where users can store files to be shared with other users."}, {"Question": "Explain the following with an example: 'In fact, with inexpensive video cameras and the right software, users can hold videoconferences over the network. Sharing these resources can result in significant cost savings.'", "Answer": "In fact, with inexpensive video cameras and the right software, users can hold videoconferences over the network. Sharing these resources can result in significant cost savings.For example, it is cheaper to buy a single high-speed printer with advanced features such as collating, stapling, and duplex printing that can be shared by an entire workgroup than it is to buy separate printers for each user in the group.", "originalSentence": "Sharing these resources can result in significant cost savings."}, {"Question": "Explain the following with an example: 'Instead, individual folders on a networked hard drive are shared. This way, the network administrator can allow different network users to have access to different shared folders.'", "Answer": "Instead, individual folders on a networked hard drive are shared. This way, the network administrator can allow different network users to have access to different shared folders.For example, a company may set up shared folders for its sales department and accounting department.", "originalSentence": "This way, the network administrator can allow different network users to have access to different shared folders."}, {"Question": "Explain the following with an example: 'You can share other resources on a network.'", "Answer": "You can share other resources on a network.For example, a network can be used to share an Internet connection.", "originalSentence": "You can share other resources on a network."}, {"Question": "Explain the following with an example: 'Nowadays, it\u2019s more common for the network to provide a shared high-speed Internet connection that every- one on the network can access.'", "Answer": "Nowadays, it\u2019s more common for the network to provide a shared high-speed Internet connection that every- one on the network can access.For example, an accounting department may have accounting software that can be used from several computers at the same time.", "originalSentence": "Nowadays, it\u2019s more common for the network to provide a shared high-speed Internet connection that every- one on the network can access."}, {"Question": "Explain the following with an example: '\u2726 Most networks have more clients than servers.'", "Answer": "\u2726 Most networks have more clients than servers.For example, a network with ten clients can probably get by with one server.", "originalSentence": "\u2726 Most networks have more clients than servers."}, {"Question": "Explain the following with an example: 'WANs are typically used to connect two or more LANs that are relatively far apart.'", "Answer": "WANs are typically used to connect two or more LANs that are relatively far apart.For example, a WAN may connect an office in San Francisco with an office in New York.", "originalSentence": "WANs are typically used to connect two or more LANs that are relatively far apart."}], "recall": [{"Question": "Over the years, _______ _______ became more and more sophisticated.", "Answer": "computer networks", "originalSentence": "Over the years, computer networks became more and more sophisticated."}, {"Question": "Now, instead of string, networks use electrical _______, fiber-optic cables, or wireless radio signals to connect computers to each other.", "Answer": "cables", "originalSentence": "Now, instead of string, networks use electrical cables, fiber-optic cables, or wireless radio signals to connect computers to each other."}, {"Question": "Fiber-optic _______ let computers communicate at extremely high speeds by using impulses of light.", "Answer": "cables", "originalSentence": "For example, fiber-optic cables let computers communicate at extremely high speeds by using impulses of light."}, {"Question": "Nowadays, network support is built into all major operating systems, includ- ing all current versions of _______, Macintosh operating systems, and Linux.", "Answer": "Windows", "originalSentence": "Nowadays, network support is built into all major operating systems, includ- ing all current versions of Windows, Macintosh operating systems, and Linux."}, {"Question": "10 _______ building blocks All networks, large or small, require specialized network hardware to make them work.", "Answer": "Network", "originalSentence": "10 Network building blocks All networks, large or small, require specialized network hardware to make them work."}, {"Question": "Every client and every _______ _______ must have a network interface card in order to be a part of a network.", "Answer": "server computer", "originalSentence": "Every client and every server computer must have a network interface card in order to be a part of a network."}, {"Question": "For high-speed network connections, fiber-optic _______ is sometimes used.", "Answer": "cable", "originalSentence": "For high-speed network connections, fiber-optic cable is sometimes used."}, {"Question": "In a _______ _______, radio transmitters and receivers take the place of cables.", "Answer": "wireless network", "originalSentence": "In a wireless network, radio transmitters and receivers take the place of cables."}, {"Question": "A whole bunch of software has to be set up just right in order to get a _______ working.", "Answer": "network", "originalSentence": "A whole bunch of software has to be set up just right in order to get a network working."}, {"Question": "One of the most important _______ choices to make is which network operating system you\u2019ll use on the network\u2019s servers.", "Answer": "networking", "originalSentence": "One of the most important networking choices to make is which network operating system you\u2019ll use on the network\u2019s servers."}, {"Question": "If the truth be told, _______ _______ are a pain to set up.", "Answer": "computer networks", "originalSentence": "If the truth be told, computer networks are a pain to set up."}, {"Question": "Because the benefits of having a _______ make the difficulty of setting one up worthwhile.", "Answer": "network", "originalSentence": "Because the benefits of having a network make the difficulty of setting one up worthwhile."}, {"Question": "Users can also hold online meetings over the _______.", "Answer": "network", "originalSentence": "Users can also hold online meetings over the network."}, {"Question": "In fact, with inexpensive video cameras and the right software, users can hold videoconferences over the _______.", "Answer": "network", "originalSentence": "In fact, with inexpensive video cameras and the right software, users can hold videoconferences over the network."}, {"Question": "In fact, providing users with access to a shared hard drive is the most common method of sharing files on a _______.", "Answer": "network", "originalSentence": "In fact, providing users with access to a shared hard drive is the most common method of sharing files on a network."}, {"Question": "A computer whose main purpose in life is to host shared hard drives is called a _______ _______.", "Answer": "file server", "originalSentence": "A computer whose main purpose in life is to host shared hard drives is called a file server."}, {"Question": "In actual practice, entire _______ _______ are not usually shared.", "Answer": "hard drives", "originalSentence": "In actual practice, entire hard drives are not usually shared."}, {"Question": "You can share other resources on a _______.", "Answer": "network", "originalSentence": "You can share other resources on a network."}, {"Question": "A _______ can be used to share an Internet connection.", "Answer": "network", "originalSentence": "For example, a network can be used to share an Internet connection."}, {"Question": "Don\u2019t wash your hands until you have these terms memorized. This fact makes sense because every user on the _______ shares the server\u2019s resources.", "Answer": "network", "originalSentence": "This fact makes sense because every user on the network shares the server\u2019s resources."}, {"Question": "\u2726 The cheaper and less powerful computers in a _______ are the clients.", "Answer": "network", "originalSentence": "\u2726 The cheaper and less powerful computers in a network are the clients."}, {"Question": "Clients are the computers used by _______ _______ for everyday work.", "Answer": "individual users", "originalSentence": "Clients are the computers used by individual users for everyday work."}, {"Question": "A _______ with ten clients can probably get by with one server.", "Answer": "network", "originalSentence": "For example, a network with ten clients can probably get by with one server."}, {"Question": "Other _______ take an alternative approach, enabling any computer on the network to function as both a client and a server.", "Answer": "networks", "originalSentence": "Other networks take an alternative approach, enabling any computer on the network to function as both a client and a server."}, {"Question": "All you have to do is enable the _______ _______ features.", "Answer": "Windows server", "originalSentence": "All you have to do is enable the Windows server features."}, {"Question": "A _______ can, in fact, contain hundreds of computers.", "Answer": "LAN", "originalSentence": "A LAN can, in fact, contain hundreds of computers."}, {"Question": "A _______ may connect an office in San Francisco with an office in New York.", "Answer": "WAN", "originalSentence": "For example, a WAN may connect an office in San Francisco with an office in New York."}, {"Question": "There are several differ- ent types of _______ topologies, each with advantages and disadvantages.", "Answer": "network", "originalSentence": "There are several differ- ent types of network topologies, each with advantages and disadvantages."}, {"Question": "_______ _______ deals with how the nodes of a network are connected to each other.", "Answer": "Network topology", "originalSentence": "Network topology deals with how the nodes of a network are connected to each other."}, {"Question": "If the cable in a bus _______ breaks, the network is effectively divided into two networks.", "Answer": "network", "originalSentence": "If the cable in a bus network breaks, the network is effectively divided into two networks."}], "mcq": [{"Question": "Each switch contains a certain number of ports, typically 8 or _______.", "Answer": "16", "Options": ["16", "19", "14", "18", "21", "13", "20", "22"], "originalSentence": "Each switch contains a certain number of ports, typically 8 or 16."}, {"Question": "\u2726 The network server features that are built into desktop versions of Windows aren\u2019t very efficient because these ver- sions of Windows were not designed primarily to be network servers. If you\u2019re going to dedicate a computer to the task of being a full-time server, you should use a full-fledged network operating system, such as Windows Server _______, instead.", "Answer": "2003", "Options": ["2003", "2007", "2009", "1998", "1994", "1996"], "originalSentence": "If you\u2019re going to dedicate a computer to the task of being a full-time server, you should use a full-fledged network operating system, such as Windows Server 2003, instead."}], "trueFalse": [{"question": "10 Network building blocks All networks, large or small, require specialized network hardware to make them work.", "answer": "True", "correctSent": "10 Network building blocks All networks, large or small, require specialized network hardware to make them work."}, {"question": "11 Network building blocks All networks, large or small, require specialized network hardware to make them work.", "answer": "False", "correctSent": "10 Network building blocks All networks, large or small, require specialized network hardware to make them work."}, {"question": "10 Network building blocks All networks, small or small, require specialized network hardware to make them work.", "answer": "False", "correctSent": "10 Network building blocks All networks, large or small, require specialized network hardware to make them work."}, {"question": "10 Network building blocks All networks, large or small, require specialized network hardware to make them work. For small networks, the hardware may consist of nothing more than a network interface card in each computer, a cable for each computer, and a network switch that all the computers plug into.", "answer": "True", "correctSent": "For small networks, the hardware may consist of nothing more than a network interface card in each computer, a cable for each computer, and a network switch that all the computers plug into."}, {"question": "10 Network building blocks All networks, large or small, require specialized network hardware to make them work. For large networks, the hardware may consist of nothing more than a network interface card in each computer, a cable for each computer, and a network switch that all the computers plug into.", "answer": "False", "correctSent": "For small networks, the hardware may consist of nothing more than a network interface card in each computer, a cable for each computer, and a network switch that all the computers plug into."}, {"question": "10 Switches can be connected to each other to build larger networks.", "answer": "False", "correctSent": "11 Switches can be connected to each other to build larger networks."}, {"question": "11 Switches can be connected to each other to build larger networks.", "answer": "True", "correctSent": "11 Switches can be connected to each other to build larger networks."}, {"question": "With a wireless network, you don\u2019t have to run cables through walls or ceilings, and your client computers can be located anywhere within range of the network broadcast. The main advantage of wireless networking is that it is inherently less secure than a cabled network.", "answer": "False", "correctSent": "The main disadvantage of wireless networking is that it is inherently less secure than a cabled network."}, {"question": "With a wireless network, you don\u2019t have to run cables through walls or ceilings, and your client computers can be located anywhere within range of the network broadcast. The main disadvantage of wireless networking is that it is inherently less secure than a cabled network.", "answer": "True", "correctSent": "The main disadvantage of wireless networking is that it is inherently less secure than a cabled network."}, {"question": "In most networks, a small hard drive on a central server computer is set up as a common storage area where users can store files to be shared with other users.", "answer": "False", "correctSent": "In most networks, a large hard drive on a central server computer is set up as a common storage area where users can store files to be shared with other users."}, {"question": "In most networks, a large hard drive on a central server computer is set up as a common storage area where users can store files to be shared with other users.", "answer": "True", "correctSent": "In most networks, a large hard drive on a central server computer is set up as a common storage area where users can store files to be shared with other users."}, {"question": "\u2726 The network server features that are built into desktop versions of Windows aren\u2019t very efficient because these ver- sions of Windows were not designed primarily to be network servers. Note that the term LAN doesn\u2019t imply that the network is large.", "answer": "False", "correctSent": "Note that the term LAN doesn\u2019t imply that the network is small."}, {"question": "\u2726 The network server features that are built into desktop versions of Windows aren\u2019t very efficient because these ver- sions of Windows were not designed primarily to be network servers. Note that the term LAN doesn\u2019t imply that the network is small.", "answer": "True", "correctSent": "Note that the term LAN doesn\u2019t imply that the network is small."}, {"question": "For example, a WAN may connect an office in San Francisco with an office in New York.", "answer": "True", "correctSent": "For example, a WAN may connect an office in San Francisco with an office in New York."}, {"question": "For example, a WAN may connect an office in San Francisco with an office in Los Angeles.", "answer": "False", "correctSent": "For example, a WAN may connect an office in San Francisco with an office in New York."}, {"question": "Again, it is the geographic distance that makes a network a WAN, not the number of computers involved. If the office in San Francisco and the office in New York both have only one computer, the WAN will have a total of two computers but will span more than 3,000 miles.", "answer": "True", "correctSent": "If the office in San Francisco and the office in New York both have only one computer, the WAN will have a total of two computers but will span more than 3,000 miles."}, {"question": "Again, it is the geographic distance that makes a network a WAN, not the number of computers involved. If the office in San Francisco and the office in Los Angeles both have only one computer, the WAN will have a total of two computers but will span more than 3,000 miles.", "answer": "False", "correctSent": "If the office in San Francisco and the office in New York both have only one computer, the WAN will have a total of two computers but will span more than 3,000 miles."}]}